One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
One Pace Premium Keep the project alive: ko-fi.com/not6ip
What's with you?! Stop this nonsense!
‫ما بالك؟ أوقف هذا الهراء‬
Why do you need to fight? You two are friends!
‫لماذا عليك خوض نزال ضدّ صديقك؟‬
Give it some time, and the two of you will cool off, right?
‫أما إن انتظرت بعض الوقت هدأ بالك‬
And Usopp! He just got fired up because of how unexpected all this was.
‫فأوسوب هو الآخر استشاط غضبًا لأنه تفاجأ فحسب‬
It's too late to back out now.
‫لا رجعة لنا الآن‬
That's not true!
‫هذا ليس صحيحًا‬
You can apologize and talk it over with him!
‫بإمكانك الاعتذار له وحلّ الأمر بالنّقاش ثانية‬
Like I said... it's too late.
‫كما قلت... ما عاد ذلك ممكنًا‬
What do you mean?
‫لِمَ لا؟‬
Usopp isn't stupid enough to risk his life over a temper tantrum.
‫أوسوبّ ليس غبيًّا ليخاطر بحياته والغضب يعميه‬
Besides, if talking is all it takes to change his mind, it wouldn't have gone this far.
‫إضافة لذلك، إن كان النّقاش سيغيّر رأيه‬
If you get it, leave me alone.
‫دعيني وحدي الآن إن فهمت الأمر‬
Luffy...
‫!لوفي‬
That's just it! The Franky Family came by this afternoon, right?!
‫ما أقول هو أنّ عائلة فرانكي أتت إلى هنا هذا المساء، صحيح؟‬
Huh? What are you getting at?!
‫ماذا؟ وماذا في ذلك؟‬
Why didn't you take the opportunity to beat them to a pulp then?!
‫لماذا لم تقم بهزيمتهم شرّ هزيمة حينها؟‬
If you had, they wouldn't have attacked Usopp, who now feels responsible for all this!
‫لو أنّك فعلت، ما كان أوسوبّ ليتعرّض للهجوم أو يشعر بالذّنب‬
Okay, then instead of going shopping, you should've stayed and kicked their teeth in!
‫كان عليك البقاء أنت وقتالهم عوضًا عن الذهاب للتسوق‬
It's the cook's job to procure essentials!
‫أنا الطّبّاخ وقد ذهبت لشراء الطّعام الضّروريّ‬
This is no time to be fighting!
‫توقّفا عن الشّجار في وقت كهذا‬
There's already been plenty of that.
‫نلنا كفايتنا من الشّجار‬
Don't argue over what can't be undone.
‫لا تتقاتلا بسبب شيء حدث مسبقًا‬
Nami...! But this idiot is...
‫...نامي-سان... لكنّ هذا الغبيّ‬
Chopper, weren't you... following Usopp?
‫تشوبر! ألم تلحق بأوسوب؟‬
I wanted to keep treating his wounds, but he turned me away.
‫أردت مواصلة علاج جراحه، لكنّه رفض مساعدتي‬
He got a place to stay in town.
‫عثر أوسوب على مكان ليمكث فيه‬
He said...
‫...قال‬
He said, "You and I are no longer crewmates, so go back to the ship!"
‫قال أنّه وأنا لم نعد أصدقاء وعليّ العودة للسّفينة‬
It's like all the great times we had before today were an illusion.
‫كل ذلك الوقت الممت الذي عشناه يبدو كحلمٍ مزيف‬
To top it all off, something may have happened to Robin.
‫وما زاد الطين بلة أن روبين متورطة في مشكلة‬
I feel like... our crew...
‫ينتابني شعور أنّ هذا الطاقم سيتفكك‬
It's ten o'clock, the promised time.
‫إنّها العاشرة كما وعد‬
Usopp will be here.
‫أوسوبّ قادم‬
You guys! Stay on board and don't come down here!
‫يا رفاق، لا تغادروا السّفينة‬
Got that?!
‫أهذا مفهوم؟‬
There he is!
‫!جاء‬
Usopp!
‫!أوسوب‬
So you didn't back down, huh?
‫أرى أنّك لم تتراجع عن قرارك‬
Just don't regret this later, no matter how it ends!
‫"لا تلومنّ إلا نفسك"‬
You asked for this duel!
‫فهذا هو النّزال الّذي أردتَه‬
Of course. Bring it on.
‫بالطبع، قاتلني بجدية‬
I'll turn the tables on you.
‫سأقلب الموازين لصالحي‬
I've already figured out how to defeat you.
‫سبق واكتشفتُ كيف أهزمك‬
Can't we stop them? Usopp is seriously injured!
‫ألا يمكننا إيقافهما؟ أوسوبّ مصاب بشدّة‬
Go inside if you can't watch.
‫اختبأ بالداخل إن كنت لا تحتمل المشاهدة‬
I'm not like your past enemies who weren't familiar with your abilities.
‫لا تضعني في نفس الكفّة مع الأعداء السّابقين الّذين كانوا يجهلون مهاراتك‬
Luffy, we've known each other a long time.
‫لوفي... عرفنا بعضنا لوقت طويل‬
I know your powers very well.
‫أعرف قدراتك حقّ المعرفة‬
What I say might surprise you, Luffy...
‫لا تتفاجأ عندما تسمع ما سأقول يا لوفي‬
I have 8,000 men under me!
‫لديّ ثمانية آلاف رجل تحت إمرتي‬
If you value your life, surrender now!
‫استسلم الآن إن كنت لا تريد الموت‬
What?! Eight thousand?! That many?!
‫ماذا؟ ثمانية آلاف؟‬
Just go inside.
‫من الأفضل أن تدخل‬
I already know you don't have any men!
‫أعرف حقّ المعرفة أنّ لا أتباع لديك‬
Usopp Spell!
‫تعويذة أوسوبّ‬
You've got razor blades running between your teeth!
‫لديك شفرات عالقة بين أسنانك‬
It hurts just to imagine that!
‫مجرّد تخيّل ذلك يؤلمني‬
Go inside.
‫ادخل فحسب‬
You've got cactus spines stuck under your nails!
‫لديك أشواك صبّار في أظافرك‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Pistol!
‫بيستول‬
Usopp!
‫!أوسوبّ‬
See?! He's in bad shape!
‫...أرأيت؟ إنّ جسده قد‬
Lethal... Ketchup Star!
‫نجم الكتشب الفتاك‬
What's that? Feeling sorry for your enemy? How arrogant!
‫ماذا؟ هل تتعاطف مع عدوّك؟ يا لها من ثقة في النّفس‬
Flash Dial!
‫دايل الوميض‬
Lethal Egg Star!
‫نجم البيض الفتاك‬
Star!
‫نجم، نجم، نجم‬
It stinks! They're rotten!
‫هذا مقرف، إنّه فاسد‬
Dammit, you jerk! Take this seriously!
‫تبًا، كن جادًا أيها الوغد‬
Think I'm fooling around?! I am serious, Luffy!
‫لا سخافة فيّ الأمر، أنا جادّ تمامًا يا لوفي‬
What?
‫ماذا؟‬
This... is how I fight!
‫هذه طريقتي في القتال‬
Take care your gaping mouth doesn't get burned!
‫اسمع، إن فتحت فمك هكذا فستحترق‬
Lethal Tabasco Star!
‫نجم التّاباسكو الفتاك‬
It burns!
‫هذا حارّ‬
Watch how you thrash about!
‫انتبه وأنت تترنّح‬
Or your feet will know my Caltrop Hell!
‫الأرضية تحت قدميك مليئة بأشواك الجحيم سلفًا‬
Ouch!
‫هذا مؤلم‬
Usopp's controlling the fight!
‫يسيطر أوسوبّ على وتيرة القتال‬
Listen, Luffy!
‫اسمع يا لوفي‬
Luffy vs. Usopp
‫لوفي ضد أوسوب‬
Rest assured, I'll beat you and take the Merry,
‫...سأهزمك دون شكّ وسآخذ ميري‬
no matter what it takes!
‫مهما كلّف الأمر‬
Lethal Pepper Star!
‫نجم الفلفل الفتاك‬
Didn't I warn you? I'm only using attacks that work against you!
‫سبق وأخبرتك. لن أستعمل  هجمات لا تنفع ضدّك‬
Dammit. It stinks... my mouth is burning...
‫تبًا، الرائحة مقرفة، وفمي يحترق‬
and it hurts!
‫هذا مؤلم‬
You won't get a chance to hit back!
‫لن يتسنى لك مهاجمتي‬
Lethal Shuriken Meteor Shower!
‫وابل شُهب الشّوريكن الفتاك‬
Smoke?
‫دخان؟‬
I'm using a breath dial.
‫أستعمل دايل النّفس‬
I take it the smell was masked by the eggs.
‫لم تلحظ الرّائحة بسبب البيض، صحيح؟‬
The smell of the gas filling the air around you!
‫...رائحة الغاز الّذي يملأ المنطقة حولك‬
Gas?
‫غاز؟‬
He didn't...!
‫...مستحيل‬
Sorry! Take this!
‫آسف، خذ هذه‬
Fire Star!
‫نجم اللّهب‬
That's some explosion!
‫يا له من انفجار‬
Luffy! Usopp!
‫لوفي، أوسوبّ‬
I am Usopp, leader of the great pirates who reign over this village!
‫أنا أوسوب، قائد طاقم القراصنة العظيم الذي يحكم هذه القرية‬
People praise me—and then they praise me more—and refer to me as Captain Usopp!
‫الناس يمدحونني ويمجدونني هنا، ويلقبونني بالقبطان أوسوب‬
You're hilarious!
‫أنت مثير للاهتمام‬
Hey, you! Don't insult me!
‫أيها الوغد، لا تهنّي‬
How come?
‫لماذا؟‬
You're one of us now, aren't you?
‫ألسنا رفاقًا الآن؟‬
I see an island!
‫أرى جزيرة‬
Whoa! Incredible! What kind of island is that?!
‫هذا مذهل، أيُّ الجزر هذه؟‬
All right! Go!
‫حسنًا، هيّا‬
Merry, full speed ahead!
‫ميري، للأمام بأقصى سرعتك‬
Full speed ahead!
‫للأمام بأقصى سرعتك‬
This is too much.
‫لا أطيق هذا‬
Luffy! Usopp!
‫لوفي، أوسوبّ‬
I figured... an attack like that wouldn't take you out.
‫أعلم... أنّ هجوم كهذا لن يطيح بك‬
I know you, Luffy.
‫...أعلم يا لوفي‬
You push your limits in every battle.
‫أنّك تقاتل كلّ معاركك بكلّ قوّتك‬
I know your abilities all too well!
‫أعرف كلّ تفصيل عن مهاراتك‬
Lethal...
‫نجم‬ ‫هيساتسو‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Gatling!
‫غاتلينغ‬
...Bursting Cactus Star!
‫الصبار المتفجر الفتاك‬ ‫ساكوريتس سابوتين بوشي‬
Ouch!
‫هذا مؤلم‬
Triple Exploding Stars!
‫سانرين كايكو بوشي‬ ‫النّجوم الثّلاثيّة المتفجّرة‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Pistol!
‫بيستول‬
Bazooka!
‫بازوكا‬
With this dial...
‫إنّها دايل‬
I absorbed the impact of your attack!
‫حصلتُ على صدمتك‬
Impact!
‫صدمة‬ ‫إمباكت‬
An impact dial!
‫!دايل الصّدمة‬
How'd you like that?! Dammit!
‫ما رأيك في هذا؟ سُحقًا‬
I am Usopp, leader of the great pirates who reign over this village!
‫أنا أوسوبّ، قائد طاقم القراصنة العظيم الذي يحكم هذه القرية‬
To our new ship and crewmate!
‫نخب سفينتنا وعضو طاقمنا الجديد‬
– Cheers!
‫في صحّتكم‬
Something like this?
‫أعتقد أن هذا كفاية‬
It looks good! Let's draw it on the sail too!
‫جميل، لنرسم ذلك على الشّراع أيضًا‬
Alright! All done!
‫حسنًا، انتهى كلّ شيء‬
Our pirate ship, the Going Merry, is finally ready!
‫أصبحت سفينة القراصنة غوينغ ميري جاهزة تمامًا‬
Gum-Gum...
‫غومو غومو نو‬
Bullet!
‫رصاصة‬ ‫بوليت‬
Usopp!
‫أوسوبّ‬
Fight's over.
‫انتهى النّزال‬
You idiot...!
‫!أيها الغبي‬
There's no possible way... you could've defeated me!
‫ما كان ليتسنى لك هزيمتي إطلاقًا‬
No... no more...
‫...لا أطيق هذا أكثر‬
Do what you want with the Merry.
‫افعل ما تشاء بميري‬
As for us, we'll get a new ship and keep sailing forward!
‫سنحصل على سفينة جديدة ونشدّ رحالنا في البحار القادمة‬
Hey! Let me sit there too, Luffy!
‫مهلًا، دعني أجلس هناك أيضًا يا لوفي‬
No! This is my special seat!
‫كلاّ، هذا مقعدي الخاصّ‬
Oh? What's that?!
‫ماذا؟ ما كان ذلك؟‬
What're you making, Usopp?
‫ما الّذي تصنعه يا أوسوبّ؟‬
Whoa! You guys! Don't just tromp around Usopp's Factory!
‫مهلًا يا رفاق، الأحذية ممنوعة  في مصنع أوسوبّ‬
Someday, I will go to Elbaf!
‫سأذهب إلى إلباف يومًا‬
To the village of warriors!
‫إلى قرية المحاربين‬
All right, Usopp! Let's make sure we go there!
‫أجل يا أوسوبّ، لنذهب إلى هناك بكلّ تأكيد‬
Let's get this party started! It's the gold-hunting eve festival!
‫تمايلوا! تراقصوا! إنه مهرجان الليل قبل البحث عن الذهب‬
So long, Usopp.
‫،وداعًا يا أوسوبّ‬
It's been fun.
‫قضينا أوقاتًا ممتعة‬
Hey, don't go, Chopper!
‫تمهّل، لا تذهب يا تشوبّر‬
Why shouldn't I?!
‫لِمَ لا؟ كان مصابًا بشدّة سلفًا قبل بداية النّزال‬
This wasn't just a quarrel or a game.
‫هذا ليس شجارًا أو لعبة‬
What's your point?! I'm a doctor! Let me at least treat him!
‫،وماذا في ذلك؟ أنا طبيب دعني أعالجه على الأقلّ‬
He lost the duel. The last thing he wants is our pity.
‫لقد خسر النّزال. كما أنّه محلّ  شفقة فوق ذلك الآن‬
Think how that would make him feel!
‫تخيّل مدى البؤس الّذي جعله كلّ ذلك يشعر به‬
Carelessly showing the loser kindness just adds insult to injury.
‫تخيّل مقدار المعاناة الّتي قد يسبّبها  اللّطف غير المبالي للخاسر‬
He fought this duel knowing full well it might turn out this way!
‫قاتلَ في نزال وهو مدرك تمامًا أنّ الأمر قد يؤول لهذا المآل‬
It's hard...!
‫الحمل ثقيل‬
That's called being a captain, isn't it?
‫ذلك هو عبء القبطان‬
Don't doubt yourself.
‫لا تتردّد‬
If you hesitate, who can we trust?
‫فإن ترددت، إلى من نولي ثقتنا؟‬
We need to leave.
‫لنخلِ السّفينة‬
We... can never come back to this ship. Not ever again.
‫...لا نستطيع العودة... لهذه السّفينة‬